hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and in this podcast I
show you how to grow your coaching
business your mentorship business get
more sales get more clients how to make
your Facebook ads work your social media
content and how to start to bring in the
cash flow that you want in your business
and today what I want to talk about is a
topic that a lot of people ask me about
when it relates to the tech aspects of
their business the funnel and the
landing page and things like that and
the and the overwhelm that I think
people feel I want to help you break
past the overwhelm this is one of the
number one things that I find that a lot
of people deal with and I wish I knew
this from the beginning and I wish I
could articulate this the way that I am
able to today right now you're seeing me
here today as I have reached a certain
place in my business where things have
become automatic and very easy for me to
be able to do and I'm able to teach this
to people in a in a very simple way that
is not complicated and so I want to
demystify a lot of the complexity I
think that a lot of people see when it
comes to their business we think that
complexity is what's going to make us
more money it's not it's not what
increases the finances for us in our
business in fact complexity is the enemy
of your goals when it comes to building
your business simplifying things and
keeping things very easy and simple the
less work that you do the less um stuff
that you have to to do the better it's
going to be you know I know a lot of us
we look at things from a bird's eye view
from up above and then we got to try to
figure everything out before we take it
I want you to tell you that that might
be your personality and by the way
that's mine as well I I I need to see
the big picture I need to know what the
facts and figures are but you need to
train yourself to be able to figure out
what are just the essentials what do I
need to focus on you know when we log in
to build our website it could literally
look like and feel like the cockpit of a
fighter jet or a space shuttle again I
don't know if yall have ever seen the
picture of a cockpit of a fighter jet or
a space shuttle very complex there's all
these controls there's all these levers
there's all these buttons that you have
to move around and things like that and
that's what it can feel like when we log
into our our platforms to build our
business I want you to realize that most
of the stuff that's inside of these
platforms whether it be the Facebook ads
manager whether it be the the um your
your website builder things like that
you don't have to know how to use all
those features you don't have to know
how everything works as far as that goes
you just have to know the basics of what
it takes to get things going so I want
to break down what those Basics are as
far as that goes again when deciding on
a platform to use I find that there's
some very simple ones I like to use
Squarespace for my landing pages but for
the last 15 years and we built multiple
businesses to over $10 million a year a
landing page has the same structure
every single time when we build it so
again when we're talking about our offer
I'm talking about a lead magnet I'm
talking about something that people can
sign up for with their email address or
something that they can use to purchase
a course or a program from you okay this
is not your website this is not the
homepage of your website and you got to
not think about it from the traditional
web sense of needing a traditional
website those don't sell very well in
your business people aren't going to
necessarily find you that way when we
Market through social media we're using
landing pages and we're using funnels
because they focus the energy and the
focused energy of the prospect we're
getting people to read exactly what we
want them to read so that we can get
them to take the action that we want
them to take okay but the problem is is
that people think well how long or short
should it be and what should it include
and all that I'm going to break that
down for you right now very simply every
landing page has at the top of
it a headline okay I I and and you're
going to notice this if you click on ads
on your social media if you click on
Facebook ads you're going to notice that
there's headlines at the top of every
page that you click on if it's related
to a coaching or a course business or
there's a free master class or it's a
lead magnet of some kind it's it's a
very bold attention grabbing statement
that makes a very bold promise it also
can handle objections as far as that
goes and it's very specific as to the
outcome and so it's more specific you
know let's say that you're creating an
offer and it's about um you know finding
your voice and being Fearless in life
okay but what you really do is you
actually help people write their books
and you help them get on
media okay and so there's a difference
between if your headline says become
fearless and find your destiny that's
not going to get anything going it needs
to be
specific get your book published and no
longer let fear run your life so that
you can start to reach the people with
your message that you were born to reach
that's a specific headline and
understanding that is very very
important now there's a sales copy side
to this as well that I want to break
down here in just a little bit after I'm
going to explain how the landing page is
structured after this we go into go into
a section that I find that most people
miss when it comes to a landing page and
and by the way in between here you might
include a graphic you might include a
photo you might include something on the
landing page that validates what the
thing is that you're trying to offer you
might include some kind of of of
imagery that talks about the thing
that's happening as far as that goes
okay the next thing right here is the
story line and everything has a story
line to it and the story that you're
telling is this and I want you to hear
this very
carefully it's the story of the positive
outcome and end
result the final outcome that the best
case scenario 1% of people that you
might
reach meaning not everybody's going to
reach this goal but the best ones who
apply it and do it and take action and
actually purchase from you in the end
and they go all the way through to the
end they might experience this and
you're telling them you're casting
vision for what is
possible you know imagine being able to
reach millions of people with your
message and not feeling like you're
stuck I remember when I was trying to
reach people in my business I was
struggling to be able to find the people
that I wanted to talk to and nobody
wanted to listen to me and I had to
learn how to communicate well and have
the conversations and the Charisma to be
able to reach people that I want to talk
to okay so so that right there is a
storyline that paints a picture of that
we can dive deeper into it as I started
to learn this my business started to
become successful I want to show you
exactly how you can be able to make six
figures with your own business become a
household name a category king or an
influencer in your space that people
trust and come after and want to and
they chase you down instead of you
chasing people down not grinding and
spending hours and hours and hours but
in fact you become an attractor of the
type of business that you want now what
I just told you is a story of the type
of outcome that somebody might
experience as they become fearless and
maybe they end up writing a book or they
end up creating a course or something
like that and they're on media so we
have the headline that grabs the
attention we have the story line that
actually Taps into the emotion because
all marketing is based on
emotion not logic it's based on feeling
it's based on getting the person to feel
something
deeply and that feeling has to resonate
with their deepest desires and even
fantasies that they
have things that might not be possible
for them
immediately and it might take time to
get there and it becomes a bold promise
that you're able to get them there then
the SE the next section on the landing
page is the what here's the problem that
I no that a lot of people do they
generally put the what first and they
don't put any of this rest of the stuff
there and they wonder why people don't
sign up they're telling people what it
is that they're going to offer and it's
purely informational you put the what
section here this is the bullet points
as to what they're going to learn and
then the last part of it after that is
the call to action this gives them the
details of where to show up when to show
up
what's going to happen and how it's
going to happen and actually has the
form where they can sign up or the
button where they can register so every
single landing page that I have includes
these four elements right here and they
go in this order every single time that
we create a landing page without
exception okay now one piece to this we
might slip under the what section right
here
testimonies okay so you're giving people
headline
what they're going to exper you're going
to you're getting them to feel what
they're going to experience and then you
tap into the logic down here and then
you validate the logic with testimonies
now you don't need testimonies and this
is a common facade and false belief that
people have is that they need
testimonies in order to be effective
with their landing pages in order for
things to actually work for them you do
not need testimonies if the story line
Taps into the right of emotion that's
directly related to what they want and
you connect it to using mirror language
to how they're already talking in their
own internal dialogue now testimonies
don't hurt it's good to have them they
do help but you don't need them and I
meet a lot of people they won't even
launch their business because they don't
have a testimony and it's like which
came first the chicken or the egg which
came first the business or the testimony
trust me the business came first and
then the testimony comes out of it and
you have to take the risk of putting
yourself out there not everybody's going
to believe you they're not supposed to
but when you can learn how to
communicate well with people on a
landing page you can start to get people
to take a risk and to take action with
you as far as that goes now when we're
writing this sales copy on a landing
page and we put these elements together
and this is not very difficult to do if
I look at every single landing page that
I've ever done in my business it follows
the structure headline first storyline
second
the what is included kind of the brass
tax and then the call to action where
they take action now when it comes to
the language of this when it comes to
the especially the language of the
storyline I think all of us can think of
the call to action and the what
initially generally that is related to
finding your Niche that's related to
deciding what topic you're going to
teach that's related to how you're going
to deliver it it might be an ebook it
might be a webinar it might be a
challenge it might be a Min master class
so almost always unequivocally we figure
out exactly what that is from the
beginning and that's not difficult and
most people know what that is in their
mind the challenging part is those first
two parts the headline and the storyline
okay headline and storyline and we've
got to think of it from that perspective
headline and storyline headline and
storyline like a newspaper you have a
headline in the newspaper and then we
have the story that unpacks what it is
to help people make a decision that's
exactly what media is that's exactly
what any form of media is including
television that's exactly what fictional
novels
are okay but I digress from this to be
able to write the sales copy we have to
understand two things what is the area
that the person that we are trying to
reach struggling
with and what is the
outcome that they desire what what are
their
frustrations what are their biggest
challenges what do they not like in
their life what do they wish was
different and then what you do is you
provide the wish fulfilled right here
the outcome you you fulfill their wish
to whatever they're struggling with and
generally what lies in between here
often inside the outcome we also do
again we have the fantasy right here we
have what they fantasize about we have
what they wish would happen and we want
to pain a picture of that the fact that
this is actually possible for them now
you want this to be rooted in reality
that people can accomplish this we don't
want to lie about it but the truth is
not everybody's going to become a
millionaire or a sixf figure earner but
you can still give them the opportunity
to become that not everybody's going to
be able to work 10 to 15 hours a week
and it might take them 5 years to be
able to figure out how to do that but
you can still provide people with the
opportunity to move the needle forward
in that direction and so what we do is
if we can understand what is preventing
them from reaching their outcome that
they want they have a desired outcome
right
here okay and anytime you're writing
your sales copy anytime you're creating
a headline anytime you're creating a
storyline you are promising the outcome
that they desire the most again needs to
be rooted in reality there's a touch of
the fantasy in
it because not everybody's going to get
there but the outcome has to be boldly
stated that by taking action by signing
up with their email address for free by
giving their phone number their wish
will be
fulfilled and that their problems and
struggles will
become
eliminated the overwhelm the struggle
the the the the what you're dealing with
and things like that and by the way
exactly what I'm sharing with you right
here this is the science behind any sort
of a sales letter any sort of sales copy
and you can actually read a book right
here again it's called The Ultimate
Sales letter by Dan Kennedy I love this
book it's one of my favorite books on
this topic early on in the book it talks
about getting into the customer what
keeps them awake at night what are they
afraid of the client that you want we're
diagnosing them what are they angry
about what do they not like what are
their top frustrations what trends are
occurring what do they secretly and
ardently desire the most what is the
built-in bias do they have their own
specific language what is there somebody
else who's trying to sell them a similar
product and who else has failed at doing
this as well and then what we can do is
we reverse engineer this into being able
to persuade people from what they are
preoccupied with that's not working for
them into their deepest desire
and we end up becoming the vehicle for
their desire to happen we end up owning
the result and the outcome for them and
saying well if you just join me and you
work with me or you sign up for this
webinar or you purchase this you get to
eliminate your struggle eliminate your
problem eliminate your frustration and
achieve the outcome of the desire that
you want and so your headline needs to
exemplify that boldly the storyline
needs to explain the highly the the the
dimensionality of this where you have
the struggle we have the outcome and we
say
listen I can help you get there and then
we list the brass taxs of how that's
going to happen we list out who it's for
we list out what the modules and the
sessions are what what the bullet point
info the information part of it's going
to be it goes beyond information when
we're actually teaching it when we're
actually sharing it it has to touch the
heart and the mind to get people to make
a decision because people don't move
based on just pure information and when
you do this this will simplify the
structure of your landing pages that was
this will simplify your sales copy
process every landing page and every
piece of sales copy and every sales
letter follows this structure we got a
headline we have a storyline and then we
talk about what is going to be delivered
with a call to action of how to take
action and I'm telling you
if you over complicate it beyond what I
just shared with you right
now it'll take you way too long to get
it up keep it simple artificial
intelligence is an incredible tool to be
able to help us optimize and come up
with some of these ideas you can use
some prompting inside of AI to do this
you can you can you can describe to it
certain things one of my favorite
techniques is this you could take a book
from Amazon the description that's in
the Amazon book on Amazon it might be
related to the top that you're doing and
you can have the AI analyze the profile
of who that's for you can have the AI
come up with what are the main struggles
of somebody who might be reading this
book what are the desired outcomes they
have and then start having it craft a
salesletter that includes empathy that's
conversational that starts to write and
create the narrative for you at least
some ideas to start with to be able to
create create this sales copy and that's
exactly what I Mentor people with in our
accelerator program that's exact what I
teach people every single week how to do
and I walk alongside them and I come
alongside them to help them build their
business and so listen I would encourage
you to jump into my accelerator program
if you are a coach if you are a mentor
if you are a course creator who wants to
get results you're tired of struggling
and you're tired of things not working
out for you and you want a solution to
stop spinning your wheels and start
getting things to produce the results
you want that's what we do every week in
the Excel elor program with our clients
I'd love to have you be a part of it all
right listen thanks for listening to
this podcast share it with somebody and
grow your life and we'll talk soon have
a good one